Guide to the Rice University Athletic Director Records (Bobby May), 1987-2005 UA 185
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Chronological, 1937-2005; 154136
  - CON-USA/ESPN Television Discussions:, 2004; 154784 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Foreman-Gillis Benefit Boxing Match:, 2004; 154785 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Fun Run:, 2004-2005; 154786 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - GPAs:, 2004-2005; 154787 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Graduation Rates:, 2004-2005; 154788 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Griswold, Julie:, 2004-2005; 154789 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Griswold, Julie:, 2004-2005; 155573 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Guests on Football Trips:, 2004-2005; 154790 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Laptop Theft:, 2004-2005; 154791 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Media Releases:, 2004-2005; 154792 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Medical Updates:, 2004-2005; 154793 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Minute Maid College Classic:, 2004; 154794 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Major League Soccer (MLS):, 2004; 154795 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Parking:, 2004-2005; 154796 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - PBS "Student Athletes" Video:, 2004; 154797 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Probations/Suspensions:, 2004-2005; 154798 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Quarterback Club:, 2004; 154799 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - "R" Room Roof:, 2004; 154800 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Rice v. SMU:, 2004; 154801 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - "Stepping Out for the Owls":, 2004-2005; 154802 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Super Bowl:, 2004; 154803 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Super Bowl Agreement:, 2004; 154804 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Transportation Services:, 2004; 154805 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Baseball Non-Roster Player:, 2005; 154806 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Baseball Super Regional (at Tulane):, 2005; 154807 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - College Baseball Hall of Fame: April 28, 2005; 154808 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Head Women's Basketball Search:, 2005; 154809 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Victor Lopez Retirement Party: April 2, 2005; 154810 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - "R" Association/Owl Club Merger:, 2005; 154811 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - 2009 Super Bowl Bid:, 2005; 154812 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - 35 Year Reunion of 1970 Basketball Team: February 25-27, 2005; 154813 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Series II: NCAA (National Collegiate Athletics Association), 1982-2005; 154844
  - NCAA Participation Statistics Report:, 1982-1998; 154845 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Division I Graduation-Rates Summary:, 1994; 154846 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Division I-A Football Championship Analysis:, 1994; 154847 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Division I-A Football Championship Special Committee:, 1994; 154848 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Division I-A Football Championship Special Committee, Report to:, 1994; 154849 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Division I-A Football Championship Special Committee, Report to:, 1994; 155574 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Restructuring:, 1994-1995; 154850 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Division I Graduation-Rates:, 1995; 154851 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - CFA: The Public and College Football:, 1996; 154852 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Division I Graduation-Rates Summary:, 1996; 154853 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - NCAA:, 1997-1998; 154854 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - NCAA:, 1997-1998; 155575 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - NCAA:, 1997-1998; 155576 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Baseball Regional Bid:, 1997; 154855 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Division I Graduation-Rates Summary:, 1997; 154856 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 1997-1998; 154857 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 1997-1998; 155577 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Special Events Committee:, 1997; 154858 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - NCAA:, 1998-1999; 154859 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - NCAA:, 1998-1999; 155578 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Championship/Competition Cabinet:, 1998-1999; 154902 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Directors of Athletics Executive Committee:, 1998-1999; 154903 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Football Media Guide:, 1998; 154904 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 1998-1999; 154905 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 1998-1999; 155579 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 1998-1999; 154906 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Division I Nominations:, 1998-1999; 154907 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Women's Basketball:, 1998; 154908 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Baseball Super Regional:, 1999; 154909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Bowl Certification:, 1999-2001; 154910 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Championship Committee:, 1999-2000; 154911 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - NCAA College World Series:, 1999; 154912 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Directors of Athletics Executive Committee:, 1999; 154913 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Division I Championship/Competition Cabinet: February -, 1999; 154914 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - NCAA Division I Championship/Competition Cabinet: February -, 1999; 154915 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Division I Championships/Competition Cabinet: July -, 1999; 154916 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Division I Championships/Competition Cabinet: July -, 1999; 155580 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Division I Championships/Competition Cabinet: July -, 1999; 155581 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Division I Championships/Competition Cabinet: September -, 1999; 154926 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Division I Championships/Competition Cabinet: September -, 1999; 155582 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Division I Championships/Competition Cabinet: September -, 1999; 155583 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Division I Championship/Competition Cabinet: September 14, 1999; 154927 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Football Certification Subcommittee Bowl Agreements:, 1999-2000; 154928 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Football Certification Subcommittee Meetings: April -, 1999; 154929 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 1999-2000; 154930 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 1999-2000; 155584 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 1999; 154931 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 1999; 154932 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Division I Administrative Committee Championships/Competition Cabinet: February-, 2000; 154933 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Division I Administrative Committee Championships/Competition Cabinet: February-, 2000; 155585 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Division IA Athletic Directors Meetings:, 2000-2001; 154934 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Baseball Regional:, 2000; 154935 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Correspondence:, 2000; 154936 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Division I Championship/Competition Cabinet:, 2000; 154937 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Division I Championship/Competition Cabinet:, 2000; 155586 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Division I Championships/Competition Cabinet: June -, 2000; 154938 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Football Certification Subcommittee Meeting: February 1, 2000; 154939 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Football Certification Subcommittee Meeting: April -, 2000; 154940 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 2000-2001; 154941 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Guide to Rules Compliance:, 2000-2001; 155587 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - NCAA:, 2001-2002; 154942 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - NCAA:, 2001-2002; 154943 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - NCAA:, 2001-2002; 155588 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Amateurism Deregulation:, 2001; 154944 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Basketball:, 2001-2002; 154945 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Divisionn I-A Athletic Directors:, 2001-2002; 154946 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Football Issues Study:, 2001; 154947 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 2001; 154948 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 2001-2002; 154949 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 2001-2002; 155589 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Publicity:, 2001-2002; 154950 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Surveys:, 2001-2002; 154951 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - NCAA:, 2002-2003; 154952 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - NCAA:, 2002-2003; 155590 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - NCAA ad hoc Review Committee Report:, 2002; 154953 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association:, 2002-2005; 154954 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - NCAA Division IA Athletic Directors' Association Annual Meeting:, 2002; 154955 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 2002-2003; 154956 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - NCAA:, 2003-2004; 154957 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association:, 2003-2005; 154958 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Gambling Study:, 2003-2004; 154959 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 2003-2004; 154960 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Meetings:, 2003-2004; 154961 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - NCAA:, 2004-2005; 154962 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - NCAA:, 2004-2005; 155591 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Division I-A Athletic Directors' Compensation Survey:, 2004-2005; 154963 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Division I Management Council: October -, 2004; 154964 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 2004-2005; 154965 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Baseball Regional:, 2005; 154966 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Division I-A Athletic Directors:, 2005; 154967 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - NCAA Fencing Championship: March -, 2005; 154968 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Legislation:, 2005; 154969 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Women's Basketball Championship: March -, 2005; 154970 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Series III: WAC (Western Athletic Conference), 1995-2005; 154971
  - WAC Athletic Budgets and Financial Aid Surveys:, 1995-1997; 154972 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - WAC Basketball TV Agreement:, 1995-2000; 154973 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - WAC Championships Committee:, 1996; 154974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - WAC Fall Meeting:, 1996; 154975 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - WAC Football Championship Operations Manual:, 1996; 154976 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - WAC Football TV Agreement:, 1996-2000; 154977 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - WAC:, 1997-1998; 154978 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - WAC:, 1997-1998; 154979 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - WAC:, 1997-1998; 155592 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - WAC Basketball Tournament Operations Manual:, 1997; 154980 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - WAC Championship Committee:, 1997-1998; 154981 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - WAC Championship Committee:, 1997-1998; 155593 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - WAC Correspondence:, 1997-1998; 155025 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - WAC Spring Meeting:, 1997; 155026 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - WAC:, 1998-1999; 155027 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - WAC:, 1998-1999; 155594 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - WAC:, 1998-1999; 155028 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - WAC:, 1998-1999; 155595 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - WAC Basketball Tournament:, 1998; 155029 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - WAC Breakup:, 1998; 155030 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - WAC Championships Committee:, 1998-2000; 155031 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - WAC Marketing Report:, 1998-1999; 155032 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - WAC Outdoor Track and Field Championship:, 1998; 155033 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - WAC Women's Basketball:, 1998; 155034 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - WAC Basketball Tournament Operations Manual:, 1999; 155035 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - WAC Comparison with C-USA and Mountain West:, 1999-2002; 155036 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - WAC Correspondence:, 1999; 155037 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - WAC Fall Meeting:, 1999; 155038 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - WAC Spring Meeting:, 1999; 155039 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - WAC:, 2000-2001; 155040 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - WAC Basketball Tournament:, 2000; 155041 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - WAC Correspondence:, 2000; 155042 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - WAC Cost Containment Committee:, 2000-2001; 155043 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association Annual Budget Survey:, 2000-2001; 155044 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association Compensation Survey:, 2000-2001; 155045 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - WAC Fall Meeting:, 2000; 155046 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - WAC Publicity:, 2000-2001; 155047 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - WAC Spring Meeting:, 2000; 155048 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - WAC:, 2001-2002; 155049 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - WAC:, 2001-2002; 155596 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association Compensation Survey: Nov., 2001; 155050 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - WAC Fall Meeting:, 2001; 155051 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - WAC Meetings:, 2001-2002; 155052 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - WAC Publicity:, 2001-2002; 155053 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - WAC Spring Meeting:, 2001; 155054 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - WAC:, 2002-2003; 155055 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - WAC:, 2002-2003; 155597 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - WAC Basketball Task Force:, 2002-2003; 155056 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - WAC Championship Committee:, 2002-2003; 155057 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association- WAC Compensation Survey: Nov., 2002; 155058 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - WAC Fall Meeting:, 2002; 155059 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - WAC-HDNET Agreement:, 2002-2003; 155060 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - WAC 6-Hour Rule:, 2002-2003; 155061 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - WAC Spring Meeting:, 2002; 155062 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - WAC Spring Meeting:, 2002; 155063 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - WAC Strategic Planning Meeting:, 2002; 155064 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - WAC:, 2003-2004; 155065 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - WAC:, 2003-2004; 155598 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - WAC Basketball Tournament:, 2003; 155066 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - WAC Championships Committee Meeting: Sept. 23, 2003; 155067 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association - Conference - USA Compensation Survey:, 2003; 155068 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - WAC Fall Council Meeting: Sept. 30- Oct. 1, 2003; 155069 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - WAC Spring Meeting:, 2003; 155070 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - WAC:, 2004-2005; 155071 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - WAC Basketball Scheduling Issue:, 2004; 155072 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - WAC Championships Committee Meeting: Sept. 7, 2004; 155073 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - WAC Council Meeting: May 2-4, 2004; 155074 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association Annual Meeting:, 2004; 155075 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - WAC Fall Council Meeting: Sept. 28-29, 2004; 155076 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - WAC Publicity:, 2004-2005; 155077 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - WAC 6-Hour Rule:, 2004; 155078 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Series IV: Title IX, 1978-2005; 154997
  - Title IX, 154998 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Title IX, 155599 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Title IX, 155600 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Title IX Self-Evaluation: Rice University, 1978; 154999 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Participation Statistics Report:, 1982-1997; 155000 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Title IX Program Components:, 1983; 155001 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Guide to Title IX and Intercollegiate Athletics:, 1991; 155002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - SWC:, 1991-1996; 155003 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - General:, 1992-2001; 155004 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Budget:, 1993-1999; 155005 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - CFA:, 1993-1996; 155006 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Compliance:, 1993-1999; 155007 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Title IX In-House Audit of Athletic Programs:, 1993; 155008 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Achieving Gender Equity: A Basic Guide to Title IX for Colleges and Universities:, 1994; 155009 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Gender Equity Recaps:, 1995-1998; 155010 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Gender Equity Survey Information - Final and Worksheets:, 1997-1998; 155011 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Certification:, 1997-1998; 155012 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Gender-Equity Study:, 1997; 155013 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Integrity:, 1998; 155014 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Division I Athletics Certification Handbook:, 1999-2000; 155015 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Draft Report - Self-Study: March, 1999; 155016 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Steering Committee:, 1999; 155017 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Subcommittee on Commitment to Equity:, 1998; 155018 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence:, 2001-2002; 155019 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - 5-Year Gender Equity Compliance Plan:, 2000-2005; 155020 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - News Articles:, 2001; 155021 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Title IX Surveys:, 2001; 155022 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - News Articles:, 2002; 155023 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Title IX Publications, 155024 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Title IX Publications, 155601 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Title IX Publications, 155602 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Series V: Barbara Tolar, 1988-1998; 155079
  - Matt Musil Football Agreement:, 1988-1994; 155080 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Sportsmanship Problem:, 1990; 155081 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Men's Tennis Rules Violation:, 1991; 155082 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Summer Baseball Proposal:, 1991; 155083 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Studies/Surveys:, 1992-1993; 155084 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Black Tie: Sept. 13, 1994; 155085 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Administration Staff Meetings:, 1995-1997; 155086 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Administration Staff Meetings:, 1995-1997; 155603 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Budget:, 1995-1996; 155087 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Budget:, 1995-1996; 155604 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Budget:, 1995-1996; 155088 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - General Notes:, 1995-1996; 155089 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Salary Study:, 1995-1996; 155090 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Summer Camps:, 1995; 155091 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - SWC Bowl Formula:, 1995; 155092 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Black Tie: Oct. 9, 1996; 155093 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence:, 1996-1997; 155094 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence:, 1996-1997; 155095 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence:, 1996-1997; 155605 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association:, 1996-1997; 155096 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Mutual of Omaha College Sports Claims:, 1996-1997; 155097 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - WAC Track and Cross Country Championship:, 1996-1997; 155098 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Baseball Regionals:, 1997; 155099 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - CFA:, 1997; 155100 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Conflict of Interest:, 1997-1998; 155101 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence:, 1997; 155102 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence:, 1997; 155606 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Gifts/Memorials/Donations:, 1997; 155103 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Martha Hawthorne Retirement Luncheon: April 8, 1997; 155104 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Medical Update:, 1997; 155105 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics (NACDA):, 1997; 155106 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - NCAA:, 1997; 155107 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - NCAA Division I Men's Basketball Championship:, 1997; 155108 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - New Football Field Surface:, 1997; 155109 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - President Gillis Staff Meetings:, 1997; 155110 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Rice University Athletic Committee (RUAC):, 1997; 155111 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Soccer Proposal - John Cape:, 1997; 155112 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - WAC Baseball Tournament:, 1997; 155113 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Series VI: Endowments, 1997-1998; 155114
  - Athletic Endowment:, 1997-1998; 155115 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Endowment Commitments, 155116 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Endowment Fund Commitments:, 1997-1998; 155117 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Endowment Fund: Gifts and Pledges, 1998; 155118 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Endowment Strategy, 155119 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Athletics Naming Opportunities, 155120 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Steering Committee, 155121 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Endowment Correspondence, 155122 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Endowment Correspondence, 155123 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Endowment Correspondence, 155607 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Financial Presentations (Rice Athletics), 155124 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Gene Hackerman Scholarship, 155125 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Owl Club Endowment, 155126 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Rice: The Next Century, 155127 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship Endowment Campaign (Athletics), 155128 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship and Fellowship Support at Rice, 155129 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Marketing, 2002; 155130
  - Marketing Committee:, 2002; 155131 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Committee:, 2002; 155608 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Marketing - Factors Affecting Attendance at Sporting Events:, 2002; 155132 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Marketing - Increasing Attendance at Football Games:, 2002; 155133 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Marketing Packet:, 2002; 155134 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Wingenroth Lawsuit, 155135
  - Assignment of Judgement, 155136 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Budgets, 155137 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Case Documents, 155138 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Wingenroth Coach/Sport Evaluations, 155139 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Evaluations, 155140 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - General, 155141 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Drug Testing, 155142 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation Forms, 155143 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Interrogatories, 155144 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Letters Against, 155145 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Letters of Support, 155146 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Bobby May Affidavit, 155147 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Motion for Summary Judgement, 155148 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Notice of Submission: Request for Oral Hearing, 155149 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Original Petition, 155150 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - PA Forms, 155151 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Psychologist Evaluation, 155152 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 155153 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Student-Athlete Handbook, Roster, Notes, 155154 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Swim Coach Position Posting/Apps, 155155 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Swim Team Meetings, 155156 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Series IX: Reckling Park, 2002-2003; 155157
  - Reckling Park Change Orders, 155158 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Reckling Park Committee Meetings, 155159 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Reckling Park Correspondence, 155160 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Reckling Park Dedication, 155161 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Reckling Park General, 155162 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Reckling Park Seating, 155163 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Reckling Park Seating Expansion:, 2002-2003; 155164 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Reckling Park Signage - Scoreboard, 155165 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Reckling Park Suites, 155166 (Box 88, Folder 9)